<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ImageProcessing</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="hdr_imaging">HDR Imaging</string>
    <string name="hdr_proposal">This will be our third of three activities. This activity will be where users can experiment with High Dynamic Range (HDR) Image processing. HDR imaging takes three copies of a photo, each at a different exposure or light level, and it superimposes them on top of each other to reduce the contrast and make the image look more natural. There will be a button in the top left that can bring you back to the launch page. The underlying code will use light sensors and the camera to determine what levels of exposure to take the picture at.</string>
    <string name="hdr">High Dynamic Range</string>
    <string name="noise_masking">Noise Masking</string>
    <string name="launch_desc">This is going to be our launcher page, and our first of three activities. This will be where users start when they open the app. It will look nice and professional, and users will be able to select one of two image processing activities. Depending on which one they select, they will be sent to one of two activities. This page will have some explaining text on it, the buttons will be labeled, and the code for this page/activity will handle switching back and forth between activities.</string>
    <string name="launch_page">Launch Page</string>
    <string name="noise_masking_desc">This is going to be our second of three activities. This activity will be where users can experiment with Noise Masking in Image Processing. Noise Masking is when a camera takes lots of dark pictures to figure out what the average random noise per picture is, and it subtracts that from the original dark image to get a better picture, since the darker a picture is, the more random noise there will naturally be. There will be a button in the top left that can bring you back to the launch page. The underlying code will use light sensors and the camera to determine how much random noise to subtract.</string>
    <string name="noise_masking_page">Noise Masking Page</string>
</resources>